feedmyapp.com 2009-12-02

# Privacy Policy Statement - Feedmyapp

## Privacy Policy

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Service](http://www.feedmyapp.com/p/terms), or as otherwise required by law.

### Information Gathering and Usage

  1. When you comment on Feedmyapp we ask for information such as your full name, and email address.
  2. Extendi uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

### Cookies

  1. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  2. Cookies are required to use the Feedmyapp service.
  3. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies.

### Client Data Storage

Although Extendi owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the Feedmyapp application and code base, you retain all rights to your data. 

### Disclosure

  1. Extendi may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](http://www.feedmyapp.com/p/terms).

### Changes

Extendi may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Feedmyapp primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to info at feedmyapp dot com or by mail at: Extendi, Via A. Diaz 60, Lastra a Signa, 50055 Firenze ITALY
